(Leonard:)She's extremely intelligent.
SHELDON: She's not that intelligent.
LEONARD: She fixed your equation.
SHELDON: She got lucky.
LEONARD: You don't believe in luck.
(Sheldon:)I don't have to believe in it
for her to be lucky.
(Leonard:)Regardless, I have a chance
at a real relationship with Leslie.
I'm not gonna pass that up for
some hypothetical future happiness...
(Leonard:)...with a woman who may
or may not want me to be happy...
...with the woman
who is currently making me happy.
SHELDON: Leonard.
LEONARD: Yeah?
SHELDON:
I still don't care.
Hey, Leslie.
Careful, Leonard. Liquid nitrogen,
320 degrees below zero.
Brrrr. Heh.
(Leonard:)Why are you smashing
a flash-frozen banana?
Because I got a bowl of Cheerios
and I couldn't find a knife.